你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府以为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第三集
他使出了浑身解数
He's making a play for it.
想当话事人
Wants to be the man in charge.
我换了个法子对付他
I got other ideas of what to do with him.
那后患呢
What about the loose ends?
我来搞定
I'll take care of them.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Nonopig  阿好  沙沙A  丢丢曳  大黑  天朝直属
时间轴：烟幕迟迟   擦擦
特效&后期：灰灰是菇凉   校对&总监：阿好
哈罗德
Harold.
有什么想对我说的吗  里瑟先生
Something you'd like to say to me, Mr. Reese?
-要是你想  -不  我不想谈
- Just if you ever want - No, I don't need to talk about it.
我是想说  要是你想喝杯啤酒
I was gonna say if you ever wanna grab a beer,
告诉我一声
let me know.
我看到它现在睡这里了
I see it's sleeping here now.
小熊很亲切的  你会喜欢他
Bear's friendly. You'll like him.
看起来可不怎么健谈啊
Doesn't look like much of a conversationalist.
确实不健谈  不过如果有人敢惹你
He's not, but if anyone ever messes with you,
他会生吞活剥了他们
he'll eat 'em.
抱歉
Sorry.
还以为我都收好了呢
Thought I got everything.
有新号码了
We have a new number.
索菲亚・坎波斯  21岁
Sofia Campos. 21.
赫克特・坎波斯的女儿
Daughter of Hector Campos.
他是巴西外交官
He's a Brazilian diplomat...
在驻纽约领馆工作  我知道
at the consulate here in New York, I know.
身为外交官的家属
As the family member of a diplomat,
她有一个临时社保号
she's assigned a transient social security number.
有你真好
It's good to have you back.
索菲亚出生于圣保罗
Sofia was born in Sao Paulo,
在瑞士接受的教育
educated in Switzerland.
她能说六国语言
She speaks six languages.
母亲五年前死于癌症
Her mother died of cancer five years ago.
索菲亚推迟了进牛津深造
Sofia deferred admission to Oxford.
陪伴父亲去三个不同的地方上任
Traveled with her father to three different postings:
柏林  米兰  莫斯科
Berlin, Milan, Moscow.
她父亲所在的政党在上次选举中
Her father's political party took some heat
因欺诈行为惹上非议
for fraud in the last election.
她的母国并不乏
Her country's no stranger
政治目的绑架案
to politically motivated kidnappings.
有消息称赫克特今年会
There are whisperings that Hector will run
参选巴西总统
for the Brazilian presidency this year.
如果有人想搞定她爸爸
If somebody wanted to get at dad,
可能会对索菲亚下手
they might go after Sofia.
难怪有保镖
That explains the bodyguard.
停下  等着
Heel. Now, stay.
你非要像狗一样跟着我
If you follow me around like a puppy,
那我只好拿你当狗
I'll treat you like one.
被宠坏的小贱人
Spoiled little bitch.
索菲亚的保镖并没有在她
Sofia's bodyguard didn't clear the store
进商场之前先探场子
before she went inside.
他可能牵涉其中
He may be part of the problem.
或者只是失职  不过索菲亚如此待人
Or just inept, but the way Sofia treats people,
有人想她死也不足为怪
it's no stretch to believe that someone wants her dead.
借过  非常抱歉
Excuse me. So sorry.
打扰一下  先生
Excuse me, Sir.
麻烦掏下您的口袋
I'm gonna need you to empty your pockets.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
-芬奇  -开什么玩笑
- Finch. - You've gotta be kidding me.
我想索菲亚现在需要一名新保镖
I think Sofia's gonna need a new bodyguard.
你想要  来个丹麦酥吗
Hey, you wanna, uh, get a Danish?
不用  谢了
No, thanks.
我在忙皇后区黑帮枪战案
I caught that gang shooting out in Queens.
那来点奇多糖如何
How about some Cheetos?
行了  弗斯科  你跟那盒子怎么事情
Okay, Fusco, what's up with you and your box?
我在那位政府雇员考文的酒店房间里发现了这个
I found it in that government lady Corwin's hotel room.
我这厢还以为
And here I thought
她案子的所有证据都消失了呢
all the evidence in her case disappeared.
那是什么
What is that?
丹顿・威克斯
看起来像是兽医
It looks like one of those gadgets
在我儿子的拉布拉多犬上装的小装置
the vet used on my kid's Labrador,
就是那种微芯片识读器
you know, one of those microchip readers?
考文为什么要在她的酒店房间放这种东西
Why would Corwin keep something like that in her hotel room?
在我看来
As far as I'm concerned,
我们牵扯到这个案子
the only reason we got involved in this
是为了把四眼儿找回来
was to get Four Eyes back,
现在他回来了
and he's back.
干嘛还要查下去
Why keep digging?
因为我们是警探
'cause we're detectives.
我这一路上学到的就是
Well, the one thing I learned along the way
知道几时闭嘴不问
is to know when not to ask questions.
你想让我接手这个吧  警探
You want me to take that off your hands, Detective?
相信我这一次
Trust me on this.
那些家伙玩的局太大
Whatever level these guys are playing at,
我们玩不起
we're not there.
准备好你的面试了吗  里瑟先生
All set for your interview, Mr. Reese?
正在评估竞争对手
Just checkin' out the competition.
很好
Good.
领馆对你的资格背景进行了审查
The consulate conducted a background check on your credentials,
处理相当麻烦
that was strenuous.
我猜猜  你只好又买下一家保安公司
Let me guess, you had to buy another security company.
还有一家信用咨询公司
And a credit bureau.
我会让你为我骄傲
I will try to make you proud.
约翰・兰德尔
John Randall?
我要看下你的证件
I'll need to see your identification.
糟糕  拿错了
Oops, wrong one.
不对  这是他的
Nope, that's his.
又错了
Wrong again.
找到了
Here we go.
抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I'm--
带兰德尔先生来我办公室
Show Mr. Randall to my office.
这些人连自己的钱包都看不住
If these other men can't keep track of their own wallets,
又怎么能看住我的女儿
how can they keep track of my daughter?
索菲亚今年已经用过半打保镖了
Sofia's gone through half a dozen bodyguards this year,
没人能跟得住她
and no one can keep up with her.
领馆保安都不行吗
Not even consulate security?
他们是巴西人
They are Brazilian,
很容易被政治贿赂
susceptible to political bribery,
暗中监视  给媒体传消息
spying, feeding gossip to the press.
我要说清楚  兰德尔先生
I want to be clear, Mr. Randall.
女儿是我的生命之光
My daughter is the light of my life,
但她确实不可理喻
but she's also impossible.
我遇到过难搞的客户
I've handled some difficult assignments.
看得出来
I can see that.
伊拉克担任过车队护卫
Guarding convoys in Iraq,
也门处理过绑架勒索案
K and R work in Yemen.
不过  你还没见过我女儿
But you haven't met my daughter.
索菲亚
Sofia.
这位是你的保镖候补人选
Meet a new candidate for bodyguard position.
不要  眯缝眼
No. Squinty eyes.
不可靠
He can't be trusted.
兰德尔先生  你被录用了
Mr. Randall, you are hired,
但如果她的隐私被泄露了
but if her privacy is compromised--
我炒了自己
I'll fire myself.
我父亲录用了你  但记住  你是为我工作的
My father hired you, but try to remember you work for me.
爸  你不是要跟
Pai, aren't you supposed to be
俄国领事共进晚餐吗
at dinner with the Russian consul?
谁会指望
But why would anyone
巴西人能准时呢
ever expect a Brazilian to ever be on time?
我还以为我们是约在八点
I thought our reservation was for 8:00.
想来也是
Of course you did.
要一起吗  索菲亚
Will you join us, Sofia?
跟你们吃饭总好过被这白痴保姆看着
这白痴之前不知道自己是来给你当保姆的
This big oaf never realized he was hired to babysit you.
你们两个相处一定愉快
You two should get along splendidly.
失陪一下  他同意见我了吗
Excuse us one second. Did he agree to meet with me?
看来索菲亚小姐
It seems Miss Sofia's
不仅只是好看的花瓶  里瑟先生
a bit more than window dressing, Mr. Reese.
确实
Yes.
要是赫克特竞选总统
If Hector runs for president,
她可是最佳竞选助力
she could be his best campaign asset.
索菲亚・坎波斯
复制手机
失败
她很聪明
And she's smart enough to
手机的无线网络和蓝牙都关闭了
keep her phone's Wi-Fi and Bluetooth turned off.
你得拿得她的手机  手动激活
You'll have to get her phone and activate it manually.
不太可能
That might be impossible.
粘在她拇指上呢
It's glued to her thumbs.
要跟我们一起吗
Do you care to join us?
已经有人害我头痛了  爸
It seems someone has already given me a headache, pai.
我还是去泡个澡  睡觉吧
I'm going to take a bath and go to bed.
走吧
Come.
司机在外边
My driver's outside.
要我把车开过来吗
Shall I bring the car around?
芬奇  有两个人盯着我们
Finch, there are two men watching us,
我要去自我介绍一下了
and I'm about to introduce myself.
宝马SUV  356C
BMW SUV, 356-Charlie.
车牌号码不全  要耗的时间比较长
You know, partial plates take time to trace.
有什么问题  芬奇
What's the problem, Finch?
你要出去吗
You got somewhere else to be?
不不  没有
No. No, not really.
放到这儿了  女士们
Cut it off right here, ladies.
你好宝贝
Hi, sweetie.
抱歉  不得不等到我父亲
Sorry, had to wait for my father
跟俄国人飞越冷战去
to bridge the cold war with the Russians.
-你朋友是谁  -他不是我朋友
- Who's your friend? - He's not my friend.
是我的新保镖
He's my new bodyguard.
我叫盖比  幸会
Hi, I'm Gabi. Enchante.
他比上一个要帅
He's cuter than the last one.
他讨厌死了
He's a pain in the ass.
没门
No way.
我跟进去  或者我们一起回家
I come with, or we both go home,
吃点冰淇淋  你教教我斯拉夫字母
eat some ice cream while you teach me the Cyrillic alphabet.
好吧
Fine.
不过你得把领带解开点
But you must loosen that tie
再弄弄你的头发
and do something about your hair.
我的头发怎么了
What's wrong with my hair?
太一本正经了
It's trying too hard.
-车牌查到了吗  -没有
- Any luck with that plate? - No.
这个  你领养的小麻烦
This distraction that you've adopted
让我无法专心工作
keeps interrupting my work.
索菲亚在干嘛
What's Sofia doing?
喝她的第七杯伏特加
Her seventh vodka shot.
你要干预吗
Do you plan to intervene?
我负责保护  又不负责管教
I'm here to protect, not discipline.
再说了  她又没在大庭广众之下跳
Besides, it's not like she's dancing on the...
看到我撩她的裙子了吗
Can you see my hand up her skirt?
明白明白
I got it. I got it!
-老兄  -你干嘛
- Hey, man. - What's your problem?
芬奇  再这么下去
Finch, if this keeps up,
忍不住对索菲亚动手的会是我
the biggest threat to Sofia is gonna be me.
不许碰我
Get your damn hands off of me.
你以为自己在干嘛
What do you think you're doing?
他袭击了无辜的人  羞辱了我
He attacked a harmless man, humiliated me.
必须炒了他
We must fire him.
我女儿被拍照了吗
Did anyone photograph my daughter's behavior?
绝对没有
Absolute not.
那我雇你的钱就没白花
Then you are doing exactly what I pay you to.
谢谢你  兰德尔先生
Thank you, Mr. Randall.
日本能源部长下午过来
The Japanese energy secretary will be here at noon.
我希望你能来
Your attendance is expected.
芬奇  赫克特在增加他的曝光率
Finch, Hector's stepping up his photo opportunities.
巴西新闻媒体猜测
Brazilian news outlets are speculating
他正在准备宣布参选
that he's preparing to announce his candidacy.
那索菲亚会比现在还招人恨了
Which will make Sofia more of a target than she already is.
去开车  我们去购物
Get the car. We're going shopping.
射频微芯片识读器
An RFID reader.
那微芯片在哪里呢
So where's the chick?
我是卡特
Carter.
早上好  警探
Good morning, Detective.
你怎么样了
How are you holding up?
好多了
I'm better. Listen.
我知道你费了不少周折
I understand that you went out of your way
帮约翰找我  谢谢你
to help John track me down, and I thank you.
没问题
No problem.
你不在身边  约翰整个人都蔫了
John's not his usual cheery self without you around.
你查到我发的不全的车牌号码了吗
Did you get the partial plate I sent?
是的
Oh, yeah.
656CDZ
656, Charlie, Delta, Zeta.
登记在一家租车公司名下
Registered to a car rental company
昨天从纽约肯尼迪机场开出来
taken out of JFK yesterday.
谢谢你  警探
Thank you, Detective.
你拿到索菲亚的电话了吗
Were you able to obtain Sofia's phone?
我现在手都是满的
My hands are full at the moment.
索菲亚  已经快中午了
Sofia, it's almost noon.
再买条裙子
One more dress.
你手里至少拿了五条了
You're holding at least five.
在这等着
Wait here.
不是说"只保护  不管教"么
What happened to, "protect, not discipline?"
索菲亚坑爹啊
Sofia happened.
那是什么声音  芬奇
What was that noise, Finch?
什么声音  我什么都没听到
What noise? I didn't hear anything.
我们似乎有点小麻烦了
We may have a slight problem.
为了追踪索菲亚的GPS信号
To track Sofia's GPS signal,
我黑进了她手机供应商的信号塔
I had to access her provider's cell tower.
索菲亚正在移动
Sofia is on the move.
看来她跟你玩声东击西了  里瑟先生
It appears she's given you the slip, Mr. Reese.
您准备怎么付款  先生
How were you planning to pay for these, Sir?
用这些付吧
They should cover it.
她在一条街外  在14街
She's a block over on 14th Street.
-快上车  -有麻烦了  芬奇
- Just get in the car. - Got trouble, Finch.
看来我得要
Looks like I'm gonna have to take out...
你好坏哦
You're bad.
我为那晚道歉  美女
Sorry about the other night, gorgeous.
是她男朋友
Her boyfriend.
拜托了  让我请你吃午餐
Please. Let me take you to lunch.
不行  我答应过我父亲
I can't, I promised my father
中午回领馆
I'd be back at the consulate by noon.
我答应过带你去下城区
And I promised you bottomless Mimosas
你最爱的小酒馆享受无限续杯的橘酒
at that bistro you love downtown.
那晚爽约的人可是你
You're the one who bailed the other night.
今晚如何
What about tonight?
我答应盖比今晚是女孩之夜
I promised Gabi a girl's night.
我叫杰克
I'm Jack.
你就是那位新保镖吧
You must be the new guy.
我会给你电话
I'll call you.
你父亲不知道你这位男朋友  是吧
Your father doesn't know about your boyfriend, does he?
他不会理解的
He wouldn't understand,
你也一样
and you don't either.
只要你出镜拍张照  你都没赶上
One photo opportunity, and you miss it.
日本人感觉受到了冒犯
The Japanese were insulted.
是我的错
It was my fault.
我们遇到了塞车
We hit traffic.
确保明晚无论如何  不能再遇到塞车
Make sure you don't run into any traffic tomorrow night.
索菲亚可不能错过
Sofia's not to miss
为巴西总统举办的欢迎晚宴
a welcoming party for the Brazilian president.
谢谢
Thank you.
我父亲不太喜欢我交往美国人
My father would want me to date someone less American.
我是为你工作的  记得吗
I work for you, remember?
索菲亚・坎波斯
复制手机
激活无线网络权限
我来查看之前电话里提过的那具尸体
I'm here to check on that body I called you about.
考文  艾丽西娅  稍等一下
Corwin, Alicia. Just give me a minute.
我登记一下就带你进去
I'll log it in and take you back.
谢了  里克
Thanks, Rick.
斯诺特工
Agent Snow?
卡特警探
Detective Carter.
你不该这样偷偷跟着我
Shouldn't sneak up on me like that.
你在找约翰
You're looking for John?
我觉得陈尸房里应该找不到他
I don't think you're gonna find him in the morgue.
多谢提醒  警探
Appreciate the advice, Detective,
不过我已经不再寻找你的朋友了
but I'm no longer looking for your friend.
我被调职了
I was reassigned.
真可惜
That's a shame.
的确
It truly is.
你伤了腿吗
You hurt your leg?
老伤了
Old mistake.
时不时折磨我一下
Comes back to haunt me now and then.
你保重吧
You take care now.
那位男士来看什么
Who was that man here to view?
和你一样  艾丽西娅・考文
Same case you are: Alicia Corwin.
我要看看她的尸体
I need to see that body.
她在冷柜里放了一周了
She's been in cold storage for a week.
上臂有道五公分的切口
2-inch incision on her upper arm.
那是正常验尸伤口吗
Is that standard autopsy procedure?
不  不是
Nope, it's not.
没有肿胀  没有血块
No swelling, no clotting,
验尸报告中也没有记录
and no record of it in the ME's report,
因此伤口一定是在验尸后才造成的
which means it must've happened after the autopsy was performed.
你把报告背过了
You memorize the report,
还是突然想到了
or you just know that off the top of your head?
不是  你刚来过的那位朋友
No, but your friend who was just here,
问了我同样的问题
he asked me the very same question.
我黑了那些不速之客
I was able to hack the rental car company
所使用的租车公司
that your visitors used.
那辆宝马租给了古斯塔沃・里拉
The BMW was rented to a Gustavo Lira,
圣保罗的一名私家侦探
a private investigator from Sao Paulo.
索菲亚在给盖比打电话
Sofia's calling Gabi.
索菲亚・坎波斯
盖比(手机)
你还好吗
Are you okay?
听上去心神不宁的
You sound distracted.
那天晚上我们见过的保罗出事了
Something's happened to that guy Paul from the other night.
-保罗  -我现在不方便说话
- Paul. - Look, I can't talk right now.
今晚到酒吧再告诉你
I'll tell you tonight at the club.
索菲亚的联系人里没有保罗这个名字
No Paul in Sofia's contacts.
我去查查她指的是谁
I'll try to figure out who she's talkin' about.
还有谁需要我们关注吗
Anyone else we should be looking at?
我们知道赫克特不认可
Well, we know that Hector doesn't approve
索菲亚的男朋友杰克
of Sofia's boyfriend Jack.
赫克特的政党
Hector's political party
呼吁社会经济领域的全面平等
stresses socioeconomic equality for all.
但自己的女儿却在外面
While his own daughter runs around town
和信托基金小子鬼混
with a trust fund kid.
我要去泡吧了
I'm going clubbing.
想走正门  换换路线
Thought I'd use the front door for a change.
明智的选择
Excellent choice.
索菲亚手机同步
已发信息：盖比
回我电话  盖比
打给我
盖比没回索菲亚
Gabi's not responding to Sofia's texts,
为什么不回我
而她之前又说不方便说话
and she said she couldn't talk earlier.
或许她身边有人
Maybe she had company.
我们也有了
So do we.
和之前是同一批
Same guys from before.
芬奇  我可能有麻烦了
Finch, I may have a problem.
古斯塔沃・里拉不是杀手  芬奇
Gustavo Lira isn't an assassin, Finch.
他是狗仔队
He's a paparazzo.
-还给我  -你在做什么
- Hey, give me that back. - What are you doing?
你父亲说不能有照片
Your father said no pictures.
马克・斯诺
中 央 情 报 局
喂
Hello?
我是卡特警探  纽约警局凶案组的
Yeah, Detective Carter from NYPD homicide.
我找马克・斯诺特工
I was looking for an Agent Mark Snow.
这是他的手机吗
Is this his cell?
喂
Hello?
卡特警探  你和斯诺特工联系过吗
Detective Carter, have you had contact with Agent Snow?
是的  我昨天见到他了
Yeah, I saw him yesterday.
在哪里见到的
Where did this sighting take place?
你是哪位
Who am I speaking with?
我们再联系
We'll be in touch.
盖比不在这儿  芬奇
Gabi's not here, Finch.
她本该在一小时前和索菲亚碰面的
She was supposed to meet Sofia an hour ago.
为什么
不回我
我到了  你在哪
没见到你
你迟到了吗
告诉我一声  好吗
我很
担心
不对劲
Something's not right.
芬奇  我发现威胁了
Finch, I think I found our threat,
他们可不是拍照的
and they're not photographers.
你怎么看出来的
How can you tell?
枪是挺明显的提示
The gun was a pretty good hint.
我的天  怎么回事
Oh, my God, what's going on?
这一晚上享受够了吧
Had enough fun for one night?
收到你发来的照片了
Got the pictures you sent.
碰巧这些人符合今晚225酒吧
Just so happens these men fit the description
被痛殴的几个人的描述
of some guys who got their asses kicked at club 225 tonight.
你对此一无所知  对吧
You wouldn't know anything about that, would you?
不合吾意啊
Not my scene.
你认出他们后颈的疤痕了吗
Did you notice the scars on the back of their necks?
印记  一些黑帮以此作为入会证明
Branding. Some gangs use it as an initiation.
我去找找哪个黑帮用这种疤痕
I'll try to find out which one uses this particular scar.
巴西海鲜炒蛋
Moqueca de ovos.
我的至爱
My favorite.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
内部消息
An inside source.
如果你今晚不在那里
If you hadn't been there tonight--
你能认出今晚的那些人吗
Did you recognize any of the other men over there tonight?
从没见过他们
I've never seen them.
可能是盖比的朋友
Friends of Gabi's, maybe.
天哪  盖比
Oh, God. Gabi.
她本应今晚在那和我碰头的
She was supposed to meet me tonight.
-那枪击  我  -我看过了
- The shooting, I-- - I looked.
她不在那儿
She wasn't there.
盖比想要谈那个保罗的事
Gabi wanted to talk about this Paul.
他是谁
Who is he?
好像是叫保罗・罗曼诺
Paul Romano, I think.
我们在周六的派对上遇到他的
We partied with him Saturday.
-在哪儿  -刚开始在酒吧
- Where? - At first, the club.
杰克回家了  他感觉不太舒服
Jack went home. He wasn't feeling well.
我气他离开
I was angry with him for leaving,
所以保罗邀请我们去顶层公寓时
so when Paul invited us back to the penthouse,
盖比和我就去了
Gabi and I went.
但保罗和我之间什么都没发生
But nothing happened between Paul and me.
从酒吧到监狱
保罗・ 罗曼诺的高危工作
我找到保罗・ 罗曼诺了
I found Paul Romano.
经营酒吧失败
Failed club promoter
数次因贩卖迷幻药被捕
with a couple of arrests for selling designer drugs.
纽约一个小小的毒贩子
What does a small-time drug dealer in New York
和巴西大选有什么关系  芬奇
have to do with a Brazilian election, Finch?
或许没关系  我不确定
Maybe nothing. I'm not sure
是她父亲的政治导致她陷入了麻烦
her father's politics have gotten her into trouble.
我开始认为也许是索菲亚
I'm beginning to think that Sofia's choice
自己的酒友导致的
of drinking companions has.
我想和这个保罗・罗曼诺谈谈
I wanna talk to this Paul Romano.
毒贩自顶层公寓坠楼
这可有点难办了
It could prove challenging.
保罗・罗曼诺周六晚从他的顶层公寓跳楼了
Paul Romano jumped out of his penthouse late Saturday night.
纽约警局判定为自杀
NYPD's calling it suicide.
索菲亚  那晚有别人
Sofia, was there anyone else
和你一起在顶层公寓里吗
in the penthouse with you that night?
我  盖比  保罗
Me, Gabi, Paul.
后来来了一个人  他一来
Then this guy showed up. He was--
气氛有点怪怪的  很紧张
things got weird, tense.
于是盖比和我就出去了
So Gabi and I got out of there.
你能形容下那个人的长相吗
Can you describe this other guy who was there?
盖比录了段视频  在我手机里
Gabi took a video on my phone.
用俄语说
Say it in Russian.
换意大利语
Now Italian.
是夜店那群人中的一个
That's one of our friends from the nightclub.
你觉得保罗和这事有关吗
You think Paul had something to do with this?
不太可能
Unlikely.
保罗死了
Paul's dead.
警方认为他是自杀
Police think he committed suicide
就在和你一起的那个晚上
the same night that you were with him.
如果保罗是自杀
If Paul committed suicide,
那为什么这些人要找上我
then why would those men be after me?
如果他是自杀
If he committed suicide,
他们就不会找你了
they wouldn't be.
你可以指证那人在现场
You can place this guy at the scene.
不止是我  还有盖比
Not just me. Gabi.
我得去找她  她也会有危险
I need to find her. She might be in danger too.
我会叫警方的朋友查看她的情况
I'll call a friend on the police force to check on her.
他们可以追踪到她的手机
They'll be able to track her cell phone.
我们必须马上找到她
We need to find her now.
不行  你得待在这儿
No, you need to stay here.
有人正试图杀你
Someone just tried to kill you.
她是我朋友  我一定要去
She's my friend. I'm going.
你拦不住我的
You can't stop me.
好吧  但等我们到后
Okay, but when we get there,
你要待在车里
you stay in the car.
-卡特  -警探  打扰了吗
- Carter. - Detective, is this a bad time?
没有  我  我只是偶然碰见了个
No. I, uh--I just ran into someone
很久没见过的人
I hadn't seen in a while.
我查到了225酒吧里那伙人身上的印记
I ID'd the branding on those bangers from club 225.
他们是14街黑手党的
They're 14th Street Mafia.
谢了  警探
Thank you, Detective.
麻烦查一下你的邮箱
Now, if you could just check your email...
认得右边这个男人吗
You recognize the man on the right?
保罗・罗曼诺  迷幻药贩子
Paul Romano. Designer drug peddler
据说四天前自杀了
who allegedly committed suicide four nights ago.
你听上去不太确定啊
You don't sound convinced.
顶层公寓的摄像机"恰巧"坏了
The penthouse cameras were conveniently malfunctioning.
这个人在保罗跳楼前和他在一起
The other guy was with Paul before he jumped.
-你认识他吗  -不认识
- Do you recognize him? - No.
但那个印记说明他也是14街黑手党的
But that branding he's got means he's 14th Street Mafia too.
我帮你查查这个人是谁
I'll work on getting a new name.
还有  我们想让你帮忙追踪一个手机号
Also, we need you to track a cell phone.
这女孩可能知道关于保罗被杀的情况
A girl who may know something about Paul's murder
可能身处险境
and who may be in trouble.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
想出去走走吗
Would you like to go for a walk?
得先找条皮带
Well, let's get a leash.
你想要点奖励吧
I suppose you'll want some treats.
卡特  告诉我你找到盖比了
Carter, tell me you found Gabi.
她昨晚没回家
She never came home last night.
手机显示她在31街和1街交界处
Tracked her cell to 31st and 1st,
所以我就来找她了
so I came down to find her.
盖比在这儿
Gabi's here.
太好了  我们这就去
Great. We're on our way.
不用了  约翰
That's not a good idea, John.
我一眼就知道这个地址是哪儿
I recognized the address as soon as it came up.
31街和1街是市陈尸房
31st and 1st is the city morgue.
巡警在下城区发现了她的尸体
Couple uniforms found her body downtown.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
索菲亚想一个人静一静
Sofia wanted some air.
我把她带到了全市唯一
I took her to the only place
能让人静一静的地方
in the city you can actually find any.
她怎么样了
How is she taking the news?
几乎跟期待中的一样
About as well as can be expected.
她最好的朋友被杀了  她很自责
Her best friend was murdered, and she blames herself.
芬奇
Listen, Finch,
我需要你过来看着索菲亚
I need you to come keep an eye on Sofia.
我要去找杀害盖比的凶手  她跟着我不安全
She's not safe with me if I'm out looking for Gabi's killer.
没问题  我很快到
Not a problem. I'll be there shortly.
我们只不过
So we'll just--
只不过出去一下
we'll just go outside.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese,
我这边情况有点复杂
I seem to be having a bit of a complication.
恐怕没法去找你了
I'm afraid I won't be able to meet you.
没问题  哈罗德
No problem, Harold.
我叫弗斯科来
I'll call Fusco.
他肯定没什么重要事可做
I'm sure he's got nothing better to do.
我不能回领馆
I can't go back to the consulate.
我父亲  会让我招待巴西总统
My father, he'll make me play host to the Brazilian president.
但我应该出去
I should be out there
找到那个杀了我朋友的混蛋
finding the bastard who killed my friend.
那是警察的工作  索菲亚
That's for the police, Sofia.
不是你的
Not you.
那晚  盖比本来不想去的
You know, that night, Gabi didn't even want to come out.
她会去  因为我说我们要去
She came out because I said we had to.
我们就要去
We just had to.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你们只是在错误的时间去了错误的地方
You were at the wrong place at the wrong time.
永远都是错误的地方
They're all the wrong places.
我迷失了太久
I've been lost for so long.
我以为只要我一直寻找
I thought maybe if I kept looking,
我就能找到让我开心的地方
I might find somewhere that made me feel happy.
我从没想过有人会因此送命
I never thought anyone would get hurt.
我有段时间也迷失了
I've spent some time feeling lost.
后来呢
What changed?
有个人找到了我
Someone found me,
告诉我  我需要一个目标
told me I needed a purpose.
似乎是很棒的朋友
Sounds like a good friend.
他就是
He is.
走吧
Come on.
弗斯科警探会陪你参加
Detective Fusco will be looking after you
你父亲今晚的晚宴  索菲亚
at your father's party tonight, Sofia.
我明白
I get it.
我没他那么高  也没他敏捷
I'm not as tall as him, maybe not as fast.
尽管拿我开玩笑  我能忍
Go ahead, make fun of me. I can take it.
你长得像我叔叔雅各布
You look like my uncle Jacobo.
我们叫他Garanhao
We call him the Garanhao.
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
种马  他可有女人缘了
Stud. He has great luck with the ladies.
别让她离开你的视线
Don't let her out of your sight.
干啥  你当我第一次吗
What's this, my first trip to the rodeo?
你喜欢[中东食物]法拉费吗
So you like falafel?
我查到了
I got an ID
录像里神秘男子的身份
on your mystery man from the video.
黑帮科查到叫蒙哥马利・斯宾塞  又名"好马"
Gang Unit ID'd Montgomery Spencer, aka Monty.
有暴力攻击和私藏毒品的犯罪记录
Record for assault and possession with intent.
他和保罗・罗曼诺之间有什么关联
What's his connection to Paul Romano?
这个我没查出来
That's what doesn't check out for me.
直到六个月前
Up until six months ago,
罗曼诺一直在向他的朋友兜售
Romano was selling small amounts
小量的夜店毒品
of club drugs to his friends.
但有传言说保罗开始卖
But word is Paul started moving
大量的迷幻药
huge quantities of designer drugs.
也许好马是他的供货人
Maybe if Monty was his supplier,
保罗想和他讨价还价
Paul tried to renegotiate his end.
看来这场讨价还价不如他意了
I'd say the negotiations didn't go his way.
有可能
Maybe.
我还是搞不懂这两个人
I still don't understand how these two
是怎么搞到一起去的
wind up in bed together.
好马多半有供货渠道
Monty might have had the hookup to the supplier,
罗曼诺有客源
and Romano the client base,
可他们谁都没有钱来提供资金支持啊
but neither of them had the money to bankroll it.
这么说他们还有个匿名合伙人
So they had a silent partner.
我不知道  不过我这有个地址
I don't know, but I got an address
是好马和他的狐朋狗友
to the bar where Monty and his pals
平时常去的
like to spend some time in.
我想我们去当面问他吧
Figured we'd go and ask him in person.
谢了  卡特
Thanks, Carter.
那不是令媛吗
Isn't that your daughter?
索菲亚  你去哪里了
Sofia, where have you been?
你还好吗
Is everything okay?
很好  只是
It's okay. I just--
来
Come.
一位巴西的老朋友想跟你打个招呼
An old friend from Brazil wants to say hello.
-这位是小女  索菲亚  -你好
- This is my daughter, Sofia. - Hi.
来电
好消息先生
既没个短信  又没个电话
You know, you don't write, you don't call.
人家虽然是大人了  但很敏感的
I mean, I'm a big guy, but I am sensitive.
我也很高兴和你通话  警探
It's good to talk to you too, Detective.
我们的朋友还安全吗
Is our friend safe?
可疑目标太多  人山人海
A target-rich environment. Lots of people.
所以我黑进了博物馆的摄像头
That's why I've accessed the museum's security cameras,
看了厨房的场景以后
and having seen the kitchen,
我建议你不要吃鲜虾泡芙
I'd advise you to stay away from the shrimp puffs.
-不如你在车里等着  -不如你在车里等着
- Why don't you wait in the car? - Why don't you wait in the car?
-给我三分半钟  -得了吧
- Give me 3 1/2 minutes. - Oh, please.
那里面至少有十个人
There are at least ten guys in there.
好吧  四分钟
Okay, four minutes.
感谢大家盛情款待
Thank you for the fine hospitality
我们尊敬的总统阁下
you have shown my country's distinguished president.
既然他也在  我想现在正式宣布
Since he is here, I think it's time to announce
我今年将会竞选巴西总统
that I will be running for the Brazilian presidency this year.
你没事吧
You okay?
我想自己待会儿
I just want a moment alone.
我就在门外
I'll be right on the other side of this door.
抱歉  我在晚宴上
Sorry, I'm at the party.
来见我
Come meet me.
我不确定
I don't know.
你答应过我今晚的
You promised me tonight.
我不确定我能出得去
I-I don't know if I can get out.
你不用出来
You don't have to.
我就在外面呢
I'm right outside.
我在车里坐烦了
I got bored sitting in the car,
你用了不止四分钟
and it took you longer than four minutes.
这家伙用霓虹灯砸我脑袋
Well, this guy hit me over the head with a neon sign,
真没运动精神
not very sportsmanlike.
他们都不肯告诉我
And none of them want to tell me
哪里能找到他们的朋友好马
where to find their pal Monty.
是啊  所以你应该先开口询问
Yeah, that's why you should ask them
然后再揍晕人家  约翰
before you knock them out, John.
里瑟先生  那天晚上还有另外一个男人
Mr. Reese, there was another man
在保罗・罗曼诺的顶层公寓里
at Paul Romano's penthouse that night,
索菲亚的男朋友杰克・休斯
Sofia's boyfriend Jack Hughes.
他就是提供资金支持的人
He's the bankroller.
弗斯科和索菲亚在一起
Fusco's with Sofia.
快通知他
Let him know.
弗斯科警探
Detective Fusco?
索菲亚在哪里
Where is Sofia?
补妆呢
Powdering her nose.
不  她没有
No, she isn't.
恐怕你去错地方了  里瑟先生
I'm afraid you're in the wrong place, Mr. Reese.
出租车
Taxi!
对此我非常抱歉  宝贝
I'm really sorry about this, babe.
抱歉
Sorry?
我不明白
I don't understand.
抱歉  宝贝
Sorry, babe.
为什么
Why?
世道艰难
Times are tough.
我信托基金的额度到了  需要钱
I ran through my trust fund and needed money.
好马有货源
Monty had the product.
我搭上他和保罗一起贩
I hooked him up with Paul to move it,
但是保罗太贪心了
but Paul got greedy.
是你害死了保罗
You had Paul killed.
不是  好马给了保罗一个选择
No, Monty gave Paul a choice--
还我们钱  或者被扔出窗户
give us the money, or go out the window.
好马是不是也给了你一个选择
Did Monty give you a choice?
你  或者我
You or me?
差不多吧
Something like that.
抱歉  宝贝
Sorry, baby.
你是个漂亮的后患
You're just a beautiful loose end.
手机交出来
Give me your phone,
马上
now.
用俄语说
Say it in Russian.
换意大利语
Now Italian.
你把这个给其他人看过吗
Did you send or show this to anyone?
很好
Good.
好了  笨蛋  好戏结束了
Okay, bozo, show's over.
快  亲爱的  下车
Come on, darling. Get out of the car.
我先宰了你  一样再抓她
I'm just gonna find her again after I shoot you.
开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
你想什么呢  以为能跑过我吗
What do you think, you're gonna outrun me?
让我琢磨一会儿
Let me mull that over a sec.
没错  我确定能跑过你
Yep, I'm pretty sure I can outrun ya.
谢了  卡特
Thanks, Carter.
受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
我没事
I'm fine.
找到杰克了吗
Did you find Jack?
还没有
Not yet.
十一点的航班  飞往开曼岛  对
11:00 flight, to the Caymans, that's right.
天啊
God!
是好马干的  我发誓
Okay, it was Monty. I swear.
他无法无天啊
He's unleashed, okay?
是他要消除后患的  不是我
He was the one who wanted to tie up the loose ends, not me.
保罗本来不用死的
Paul was never even supposed to die.
求你了  你想要什么
Please. What do you want from me?
这是勒索吗
Is this a shakedown?
不  这是分手
No. This is a breakup.
索菲亚  要我把他扔下去吗
Sofia, should I drop him?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
先别扔
Not yet.
你杀了我唯一的朋友
You killed my only friend.
那不是我的主意  宝贝
That was so not my idea, baby.
就像把我出卖给好马也不是你的主意一样
Just like selling me out to Monty wasn't your idea?
我说了他让我选择
I told you he gave me a choice,
你或者我
you or me.
你有他  我就知道你会没事的
You have him. I knew you'd be okay.
我会没事的
I will be okay.
? She was made to blow you away ?
?She don't care ?
?what any man say ?
进去
Get in.
感觉好舒畅
That was fulfilling.
-谢谢你  -没问题
- Thank you. - No problem.
想过你接下来要做什么吗
Have you thought about what you'll do next?
我要跟我父亲回巴西
I will be returning to Brazil with my father
开始竞选
for the election.
我想我没法说服你一起走
Guess I can't talk you into relocating?
纽约是我的家
New York's my home...
目前是
for now.
你把我照顾得很好
You've taken very good care of me.
晚安
Night.
卡特警探  你致电中情局
Detective Carter, did you call the CIA
问过马克・斯诺
regarding Mark Snow?
我打过他的手机  是的
I called his cell, yes.
你和马克・斯诺联系过
You had contact with Mark Snow.
据我所知  监视斯诺的人是你
Last I checked, Snow was yours to keep tabs on,
不是我
not mine.
你跟丢了
You lose him?
我本来要说去找他的搭档伊万斯
I'd say talk to his partner Evans,
不过那家伙五周前死在一家酒店里
except the guy was found dead in a hotel five weeks ago.
我替你做的工作够多了
Think I've done enough of your job for you.
现在  恕我失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me.
? Her eyes?
? they're rubies and pearls?
? She's not made?
刚刚去了陈尸房
Dropped by the morgue.
从考文的尸体上取出了点东西
Got something off Corwin's body.
是我们想的吗
Is it what we thought?
初步看了一下
Took a preliminary look at it.
我想我们有大麻烦了
I think we have a big problem.
你还要多久能到
How soon can you get here?
? She was made to blow you away?
? She don't care?
考文死了
Corwin's dead.
你对此可没什么发言权  马克
Not sure you're the best judge of that, Mark.
你还认为我也死了呢
I mean, you thought I was dead too.
总得乐观一点吧
Always been a bit of an optimist.
你想知道是谁让她派遣你
You wanna know who told her to send you
和里瑟到中国去
and your pal Reese to China,
你得使劲大声吼问她了
you'll have to ask her really loudly.
可惜
Shame.
看来你要为我多跑几趟了
Guess you'll have to run a few more errands for me.
我告诉你  做我们这行的
I gotta tell ya, our line of work,
会遇上很多心理不正常的人
you meet a lot of disturbed people,
但是你  卡拉
but you, Kara?
你总能自成一派
You were always in a class all by yourself.
小心一点
Be careful.
可别伤害我的感情
Wouldn't wanna hurt my feelings.
也许我会忘记你在这里了
I might forget you down here.
? Her lashes flap ?
? and they smack men back ?
? like springs bouncing off of her curls ?
? Oh, yeah ?
? She's long ?
? long gone ?
该去喝那杯啤酒了
It's time we went for that beer.
我有事情要处理
I need to wrap things up here.
那些可以等
Things here can wait.
非得是啤酒吗
Does it have to be beer?